(Emily:)so if you get scared,
I can totally change your diaper.
(Raj:)Actually, I have to
tell you something.
(Raj:)These kind of movies
really aren't my thing,
(Raj:)so, last night, I watched it just
to see what I was getting myself into.
(Leonard:)-Okay.
-And I have to be honest.
(Raj:)I thought it was disturbing
and weird,
(Raj:)and it made me wonder what it says
about someone who enjoys it.
(Emily:)I wonder that too.
(Raj:)Then why do you
watch these things?
(Emily:)Can I tell you something
without you judging me?
(Leonard:)Sure.
(Emily:)They kind of turn me on.
(Raj:)And play.
(Sheldon:)Hello. I didn't expect you
this evening.
(Amy:)Well, I was just feeling so bad
about lying to you the other night,
l... wanted to make it up to you.
(Sheldon:)And how do you propose to do that?
(Sheldon:)Unless you have Gravity
on Blu-ray under that skirt,
(Sheldon:)I don't know where
you're going with this.